#### DIGITAL MARKETING OBJECTIVE

Work On Search engine optimization (SEO), Google Adwords (SEM), Social Media Optimization (SMO), Social Media Marketing (SMM) and Email Marketing services to different clients as required by them.

• Performed a roadmap and strategy for identifying the best digital marketing techniques based on the nature of the business and its target audience.

• Efficiently handled search engine optimization (SEO) for the client websites and played a vital role in making the website presence on SERP results and hence generating business.

#### **CONTACT ME AT**

- Dilshuk Nagar, Hyderabad Konark Theatre Lane, 500060
- oyeoy94@gmail.com
- www.digitalsiddhu.com
- in @KRangaswamy
- 8247657057

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Project Management
- •••• Website Development
- •••• Budgeting and Cost Analysis
- •••• Social Engagements, Generate leads
- ••• Advertising, Creating Paid Campaigns
- •••• Improving Online Presence

#### AWARDS RECEIVED

- Certification In Digital
  Marketing Course
- Certifications In Google
  Ads, Display Ads, Text Ads

# **K RANGASWAMY**

#### PERSONAL PROFILE SUMMARY

Hello,My Name is Rangaswamy and I am a Digital marketing Executive With 1+ Years Experience in Implementing a wide array of Digital marketing & Advertising Techniques to promote Brand Awareness,increase Customer Engagement,and meet sales and brand objectives as well as search Engine optimization principles.

# SEO Internship ( Paid ) At Suresh Productions

- I Did Internship At Suresh Productions For 3 Months
- Work On Youtube SEO to Increase Views And Engagement
- Optimizing Video Titles And Tags And Descriptions.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## SEO Analyst

# Nestack Technologies | Oct 2021 - Aug 2022

- Working as a SEO Analyst at Nestack
- Successfully Ranked Targeted Keywords 1st Position On SERP Results From Zero Rank.
- Performed On Keyword Research & SEO Site Audit
- Optimizing Website Architecture & Content
- Implementing On-Page And Off-Page SEO Techniquies
- Reporting Weekly And Monthly Reports to Management

# **Digital Marketing Executive**

### Connate Software Solutions | April 2021-Dec 2021

- Design And Executed A Highily Effective SEO Campaigns
- Daily Postings on Social Media Sites
- Creating Facebook And Google Adwords Campaigns
- Increased Site Traffic And Brand Awareness From Paid Sources (Google Ads, Facebook Ads, Video Marketing)

#### EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

# Digital Marketing Course - Digitalnest Digital Marketing Course | Feb 2021- Mar 2021

- Learnt Advanced Digital Marketing Concepts With Practical Knowledge
- Studied project planning, coordination, And Hands on Live Projects.
- Worked with Live Projects And Developed Own Website

# Avanthi Group Of Engineering Colleges, Hyd B.Tech in Civil Engineering | 2014 - 2018

 Graduated From Avanthi Group Of Engineering Colleges Wth GPA: 69.2 (%)